Guide to the Larry Palmer papers, 1972-2011.
Palmer, Larry papers, 1972-2011.
- Series VIII. Research Subject Files
  - Policing the Police Power: Bioterrorism and Public Health Law (Box 28, Folder 15-16)
  - ACNP Study Group, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Pedagogy, 2007 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Health Care System, 2008 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Genetics and Law, 2004-2007 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Medical Use of Marijuana, Michigan, 2008 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Washington State Ballott 2008, Death With Dignity Act, 2008 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Massachusetts: State Income Tax Initiative, 2008 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Initiatives: Gay Rights, 2008 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Articles: Irma N. Ramos, 2001-2004 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Articles: Linda Nozzick, 1995-1997 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Articles: Paul Lambardo, 2005 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Articles: Adult Learning (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Behavioral Economics and Health Policy: Understanding Medicaid's Failure, 2005 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - National Patient Safety - Review, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Quarantines and Distributive Justice, 2005 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Articles: Miscellaneous, 2004-2007 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Articles: Health Law, Miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Cervical Cancer (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Implantable Cardioverter-Defibrillator (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Liability, Regulation and Policy in Surgical Innovation (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Cardiovascular Disease Risk and Research (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - ERISA (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Action Research (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Series IX. Additional Material
  - Physician Assisted Suicide Articles, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Articles, 1986-1994 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Patient Safety, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Reuschlein Lecture, April 4, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Library Search Results, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Truth and Reconciliation Commission, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - University Committee on Human Subjects, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Bioethics, Minorities and the Law: Rights and Remedies, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - New York Presbyterian Patients Rights, with Cassette (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Visiting Scholar Project, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Yudowitz Lecture, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 11-12)
  - Hastings Center, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Death and Dying, L. Palmer, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Sperm Donor Rights, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Summer Writing Problem, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Complaint Tuskegee Syphilis Study, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - ACLA Interdisciplinary Studies, Yale University, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Renee C. Fox Articles and Correspondence, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Medical Liability for Pharmacogenomics, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Pharmacogenomics and Population Groups, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Cornell School of Industrial Labor Relations Information Packet, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - University of Louisville School of Medicine Information, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Miscellaneous Articles, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Oregon v. John Ashcroft, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Lymerix Litigation Articles, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 26-28)
  - Kaiser Foundation Information, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Sarah Norris, Presidential Scholars, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Yudowitz Lecture Luncheon, June 9, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Biology and Society Advising Materials, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - FACTA, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - "Writing Law" Agreement, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - NPSF Education Committee, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - William B. Palmer Memorial Lecture, May 1 2002 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - South African Medicine Articles, 1997-1998 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Supervised Writing on Patent Law Articles, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Surrogacy Articles, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - LR Research Solution, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - American Comparative Literature, February 25-27, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Experimentation with Human Beings Paper, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Diabetes Self Management (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Biobanks and Liability Research Articles and Drafts, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 4-6)
  - Sharona Hoffman Articles, 1999-2002 (Box 13, Folder 7-8)
  - Genes and Disability: Defining Health and the Goals of Medicine Symposium, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - "Looking for Trouble in All the Right Places" - L. Palmer, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Research: Right to Die, Quinlan Briefs, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 11-12)
  - Physician Assisted Suicide Articles, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1983-1994 (Box 13, Folder 14-23)
  - Barber v. Superior Ct., 1989 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - The Matter of Karen Quinlan, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Cruzan v. Harmon, The Right to Die, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - International Union, UAW v. Johnson Controls, Inc., 1989 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Various Newspaper Clippings, Medical Law Issues. Labels on Folders, 1989-1991 (Box 13, Folder 28-41, 46)
  - Articles on Alternative Therapies in Australia, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Pregnancy Articles, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Boycott of Chiropractors Articles, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Research on Human Subjects Article (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Fetal Rights (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Right to Die Materials, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Christine Overall, Access to In Vitro, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Sperm Donors, Abortion Articles, 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 50-51)
  - Mary O'Connor v. Westchester Medical Center, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Turnock v. Ragsdale, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Bowers v. Hardwick, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - Men's Rights in Abortion Debate, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Castration of Sex Offenders (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Liberty Interest, Loving, Moore, Griswold, 1965-1975 (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - German Medicine Articles, Correspondence, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - Hodgson v. Minnesota, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - Hodgson v. Akron, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - Research: Malpractice Diabetes Self Management, 1979-1988 (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
  - Research: Right to Die, 1983-1986 (Box 14, Folder 3-4)
  - Kevorkian Case Transcripts, Tapes 1-15, 27, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 5-12)
  - Dr. Quill's and Dr. Kevorkian's Constitutional Rights Editorial, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Kevorkian Case Project, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 2,5)
  - Writing Law Lecture, Fall 1998 (Box 15, Folder 3-4)
  - Funding Sources, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Bronx Medically Underserved Research, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Corporate Compliance Outline of Written Manual (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Michael H. vs. Gerald D., 1988 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Surrogacy Article (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Invitro Custody Case, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Holtzman vs. Knott, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Moore vs. City of East Cleveland, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Bottoms vs. Bottoms Custody Case, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Davis vs. Davis Embryo Custody Case, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Assisted Suicide Conversation, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - California Institute of Technology Lecture, January 18, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Kevorkian Tape Transcripts, Tapes 16-29, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Vacco v. Quill and Washington v. Glucksberg Briefs (floppy disc copy included), 1997 (Box 15, Folder 19-20)
  - Kevorkian Trial Articles, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Holland Lecture, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Hemlock Materials, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Various Physician Assisted Suicide Articles (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Physician Professional Misconduct Cases, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Kevorkian Case Summary, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Jurimetrics, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Housing Documents, June 1994 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Rivier College Lecture, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Maryland Lecture and Article, 1996-1997 (Box 15, Folder 30-32)
  - ASHP Role of Pharmacist in Assisted Suicide, 1997-1998 (Box 15, Folder 33-34)
  - Human Reproduction Articles and Research, 1996-1997 (Box 15, Folder 35-36)
  - Exploration in the Law and the Legal Profession Summer Lecture, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Review of Komesar's Book, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 38-42)
  - Aspen Institute Seminar, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Various Academic Affairs Information, 1993-1994 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Physician Assisted Suicide Articles, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - New York State Bar Association Correspondence, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - NYS Bar Ethical Delivery Membership List, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - "Susceptible to Kindness: Miss Evers Boys" Contracts, Correspondence, Analysis, Video Information, 1994-1999 (Box 16, Folder 5-12, 14)
  - Software/Computer Information, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Wesleyan University Dean Of College Statements, 1995-1997 (Box 16, Folder 15-16)
  - Miscellaneous Pamphlets and Correspondence, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Princeton Visit: Middle States Report, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Shared Journey Information, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence with Roberta Artmstrong, 1987-1995 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Book Chapters Correspondence, 1995-1997 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Ruth Scheuer Recommendation, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Davydd Greenwood and Morten Levin Manuscript Information and Correspondence, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Lois Shepherd Tenure Material, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Biomedical Ethics and Morals Panel Discussion, April 12, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - MayDay Fund Proposal, July 1, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Thomas Rodziewicz Correspondence and Articles, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - "Dying With Strangers" Publishing Information, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Patient Safety Foundation Information, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Proposal on Patient Safety and Accountability, 1997-1998 (Box 16, Folder 30-31)
  - NSF Proposal Drafts, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - APS Patient Safety Proposal Correspondence and Information, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Kaiser Proposal, Articles and Information, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 34-36)
  - Robert Wood Johnson Proposal, 1998-1999 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Managing Mistakes in Medical Care, Weill Medical College Conference - Lecture slides, notes, presentations, transparencies, June 1, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 1-5)
  - A Proposal for a Cornell Center for Medical Ethics - Joseph Fins, January 30, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Law and Medicine Articles (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Legistlation Articles (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Patient Safety - Kaiser Project Artticles (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Committee for Research and Error Reduction Information and Meetings, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 10-14)
  - Cornell Presidential Scholars, October 18, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Ethics Initiatives, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - NYS Bar Association Meeting, October 19, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Committee on Ethical Issues in the Provision of Health Care, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Critical Issues in the Future of the Health and Health Care of the American People, May 27, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, July 11, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Executive Committee, Health Law Section NYSB, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - "Educating the Reflective Legal Practitioner" - edited talk by Donald Schon (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Donald Schon Book Review, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Andrew Goldsmith Articles, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Patient Safety Proposals, September, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Innovation Program Project, December 1998 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Confidentiality Agreement, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Patient Safety- HCFA Proposal, January 5 2000 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Reviewers' Comments on National Patient Safety Foundation Proposal, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - National Patient Safety Foundation Board Meeting, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 40-41)
  - National Patient Safety Foundation Development Committee, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - National Patient Safety Foundation Board of Directors, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Book Reviews and Disk, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Ithaca College Cloning Talk, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Emerging Problems in Urban Public Health Course Materials, Fall 2007 (Box 37, Folder 29-34)
  - University Committee on Conflicts, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Merck Visiting Scholar, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Higgingbotham Clerks, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Various Cases and Memoranda, 1991-1994 (Box 18, Folder 1-5)
  - Miscellaneous Articles, 1990-1995 (Box 18, Folder 6-7)
  - Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 8-9)
  - Correspondence, 1987-1991 (Box 18, Folder 10-11)
  - Biotechnology and the Law Committee Membership, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Association of America Law Schools, 1988-1993 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - New York State Bar Association, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Biotechnology and the Law Committee Travel, 1989-1992 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Statutes, 1987-1993 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Biotechnology and the Law Committee Minutes, 1987-1993 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Biotech Report, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Biotech Report, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Surrogacy Report, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Biotech Report and Reference Manual, 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - American Society of Health-System Pharmacists, DEcember 8, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Articles from Gary Stein, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - 19th Annual Health Law Teacher's Conference Materials, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 16-18)
  - 3rd Annual Northeast People of Color Conference Materials, March 27-29, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Asthma, Allergy and Immunology Finger Lakes Medical Conference Materials, June 12, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 20-25)
  - L. Palmer Employment Information, 1969-1999 (Box 19, Folder 27-29)
  - L. Palmer Personal Writings, 1984, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 30-31)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Larry Palmer Letters of Support, 1988-1991 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Conflict of Interest Statements, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Faculty Appointment Reviews, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - L. Palmer Job Nominations, 1984-1990 (Box 19, Folder 36-37)
  - Congratulatory Correspondence and Honors, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Tax Information (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Biotechnology and the Law and NYSBA Panel, January 1994 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Biotech Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Larry Palmer Resume (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Consultation Exploration, 1993-1999 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Center for Applied Research, 1994-1997 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Scholar Round Table Group, June 12, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Accel Partners Information, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Directorship Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Phillips Exeter Academy Principal Search, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Rodman Moorhead, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - RIT, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - Paris, Spring 1999 (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - British Conjoined Twin Case, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - Colorado University Talk, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - Kendall Talk, September 21, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - New York State Bar Association Certificate and Photograph (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - Nick Salvatore: Letters and Speech, 2005-2006 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Computer Usage Techniques, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Obesity, 2007 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Vaccine Policy, 2007 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Air Quality, 2007 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Innovative Surgical Procedures, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Milken Institute Study and Miscellaneous Articles., 2005 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Heather Harrell Senior Research HPV Vaccine (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Emerging Problems in Urban Public Health, 2007 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Pandemics - Public Health, 2005-2007 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Introduction to Urban Health, 2007 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Health Policy and Law Initiative Draft - Larry Palmer, 2008 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - European Health Care Studies, 2008 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Various Court Case Notes (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Laura Hogan - Research Assistant Information, 2008 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous Drafts (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Patient Safety Articles (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Pharmaceutical Economics and Policy Proposal (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - David Cifu Grant (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Union PSCE - President's Advisory Council, 2008 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - American Lung Association - Leadership Board, 2008-2009 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Team Meetings, 2008 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - School of Public Health - Strategic Plan (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - School of Public Health - Dean Search, 2008 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - School of Public Health - Administrative Council, 2008 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1999-2001 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Meetings with Laura Sminoff - VCU, 2008 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - VCU/Massey - Postdoctoral Training - Cathy Bradley, 2008 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Williamsburg Community Health Foundation - Program, 2008 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Jessie Ball-duPont Grant, 2008-2009 (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia Commission on Mental Health Law Reform, 2008 (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - Hastings Center: Finance Committee, 2009 (Box 34, Folder 47)
  - Supreme Court Case: Colden Gate Restaurant Association vs. City and County of San Francisco, 2009 (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - The Role of ERISA Preemption in Health Reform: Opportunities and Limits - Peter Jackson (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - Hastings Center Minutes of the Meeting of the Board of Directors, September 2009 (Box 35, Folder 35)
  - VCU Health Administration PhD Student, 2009 (Box 35, Folder 37)
  - Race, Ethnicity and Language Articles (Box 35, Folder 43)
  - Miscellaneous Articles (Box 35, Folder 76)
  - New Directions in American Health Care, March 11-12, 2010 (Box 35, Folder 77)
  - Interdisciplinary Health Policy Internship, June 16, 2010 (Box 35, Folder 78)
  - Michael Bagel Meetings, June 29, 2010 (Box 35, Folder 79)
  - Articles on Texas Nurses, 2010 (Box 35, Folder 86)
  - Articles on McAllen, Texas, 2009 (Box 35, Folder 87)
  - Miscellaneous Research Articles Involving Texas (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Interdisciplinary Health Care Policy Internship, Summer 2010 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - VCU Graduate School Curriculum Approval request forms, Fall 2010 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Articles, April 2011 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Risk-Benefit Consideration in Drug Regulatory Decision-Making (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - MHA Admissions Committee, 2009-2010 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - US Department of Health and Human Services Appreciation Certificate to Larry Palmer, 2011 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Photograph of Larry Palmer (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Accountability Project: Drafts and Articles, 2000 (Box 37, Folder 35-38)
  - Publications with Articles by Larry Palmer (Box 38)
    Publications include but are not limited to: The Journal of Criminal Law and Criminology, The New Yorker, University of Pennsylvania Law Review, and the Georgetown Journal on Poverty Law and Policy.
  - Digital Media Files (Box 38)
    Includes Cornell Teaching and Provost Files, various presentations, and research and correspondence
- Series X. Audio Visual Material
  - Cornell Medical and Cornell Law, Physician Assisted Suicide, Legal and Ethical and Medical Issues, Larry Palmer, Joe Fins, Suzanne Stonsaas, 1 disc (Box 20)
  - Michigan vs Jack Kevorkian case, recordings from the trial, 1993; 14 tapes (Box 20)
  - Court TV coverage of the Michigan vs Jack Kevorkian trial. Trial Story, 1993; V-5753 (Box 20)
  - Court TV coverage of the Michigan vs Jack Kevorkian trial., 1993; V-5753-5782 (Box 20)
  - Court TV aircheck, 4-5, 5-6, 6-7 and 7-7:30., January 23, 1997; V-5783-5786 (Box 20)
  - Physician Assisted Suicide Palmer Interview, Master, January 17, 1996; V-5787 (Box 20)
  - Physician Assisted Suicide Interview, Palmer, Galbreath, Bernstein, V-5788 (Box 20)
  - Physician Assisted Suicide Interview, Garvey, Cook, Simmson Part 1., V-5789 (Box 20)
  - Physician Assisted Suicide Interview Simmson Part 2., V-5790 (Box 20)
  - Physician Assisted Suicide Interview, Palmer, Clymer., V-5791 (Box 20)
  - Copy two of Court TV coverage of the Michigan vs Jack Kevorkian trial. Time coded., 1993; V-5792-5820 (Box 21)
  - Susceptible to Kindness: Miss Evers' Boys and the Tuskegee Syphilis Study, 3 labeled advance copies, New York State Library Association., October 20, 1994; V-5821-5824 (Box 21)
    -also contains DVD-1207, a copy of V-5821
  - Miss Evers' Boys Performance Act I and Act II Rough 3rd generation VHS., V-5825-5826 (Box 21)
  - Tuskegee Apology, May 15, 1997; V-5827 (Box 21)
  - "Frankenstein" Community Panel Discussion at Barton Hall Cornell University, August 25, 2002; V-5828 (Box 21)
  - An American Festival at Cornell Roadside Theater JuneBug theater., V-5829 (Box 21)
  - Roadside Theatre: Macneil / Lehrer, V-5830 (Box 21)
  - Beyond Hate, V-5831 (Box 21)
  - unlabeled tape, V-5832 (Box 21)